# Adam Marchlewski

48 728 807 683

hello@adammarchlewski.com

in/adammarchlewski | Warsaw, PL

One of a kind specialist with 3+ years of music industry experience.

Dedicated to empowering artists and promoting culture through innovative strategies. Fluent in managing partner relations, channel marketing and crossfunctional projects. Polish hip-hop geek.

## **EDUCATION**

## **Adam Mickiewicz University, BA**

2017 - 2021 | Poznan, Poland

Field of studies: Journalism & Communications

Specialization: Online Marketing

Thesis title: The use of social media and web-based platforms in marketing communication on the music market. ℰ

# **SOFTWARE**

Asana | Slack | Workday

Airtable | Tableau | Databricks

Adobe CC | Meta for Business

Figma | Google Suite | xAdmin

#### **SKILLS**

Agility • Creativity

Problem solving • Communication

## **CERTIFICATES**

**Digital Strategy** *∂* 

**Communications Strategy**  $\mathscr O$ 

**Communication Foundations** *⊘* (*Project Management Institute*)

Project management for Creative Projects *∂* 

Market Research: B2B ∂ (LinkedIn)

## REFERENCES

Nawojka Chałupińska,

Head of Partner Marketing EMEA, TIDAL nawojka@tidal.com

**Ewa Zamojska**, *VAS Manager*, Vectra e.zamojska@vectra.pl

**Maciej Maj**, *A&R*, Sony Music Poland maciej.maj@sonymusic.com

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **TIDAL**

Content & Partnerships Marketing Specialist

Apr 2023 - present

- Complex project management executing migrations of major partnerships, including contract termination, communications planning and negotiating business offer details;
- **Campaign launches** participating in major product launches and coordinating own areas of a project, including delegation of tasks;
- Innovation creating custom-tailored, automated solutions to streamline day to day work

**Projects:** TIDAL RISING Poland launch ∅ (Sep 2023), United Group partnership ∅ termination (Jan 2024), TIDAL Retiering launch ∅ (Apr 2024)

Content & Partnerships Marketing Associate

Feb 2022 - Apr 2023

- Key account management Exclusive responsibility for maintaining business relationships with Vectra, Canal+ and Mastercard:
- Partner marketing Coordinating and executing product marketing efforts in own channels as well as securing promotional opportunities in partner-owned channels;
- Customer acquisition Creating non-standard content based activations for partners, reporting and measuring campaign results

**Projects:** TIDAL x Sun Festival S2W Contest ∂ (Jul 2022), TIDAL Live Mode launch in Warsaw and Berlin ∂ (Apr 2023)

#### **Junior Editor**

Jan 2021 - Feb 2022

- **Curation** creating hand-picked editorial playlists for the second largest DSP audience in Poland;
- Artist and label relations serving as the main point of contact for label and distribution partners (Sony Music, Universal Music Group, Warner Music Group, MyMusic, e-Muzyka among others);
- Social media consulting and approving content used on TIDAL's CEE social handles, producing own formats, creating and executing non-standard activations for brand partners (Desperados, Play, Polkomtel among others)

**Projects:** TIDAL x Cybex by DJ Khaled *⊗* S2W Contest (Jun 2021), New pricing launch *⊗* (Nov 2021), TIDAL x Sentino Instagram takeover *⊗* 

#### Radio Meteor, Host

Feb 2018 - Feb 2020

# **PROJECTS**

Polski Rap, Marketing support 🤌

Nov 2023 - present

- Social management creating and executing a holistic strategy
- Assets ideation and production of static assets and post copy
- Campaign setup identifying a target group and creating ad campaigns in Meta for Business

Bohema 2.8, Airtable interface setup 🔗

Feb 2024